(Sheldon:)Oh, you think you're so clever.
(Sheldon:)Well, let me just tell you.
While I do not currently have a retort...
(Sheldon:)...check your e-mail periodically
for a doozy.
(Leonard:)So much for our friendship with Sheldon.
(Raj:)Well, we'll always have the night
the heat went out.
(Raj:)-Hi.
-Hey.
Since we got interrupted last night,
I didn't have a chance to give you this.
Aw, Leonard. You shouldn't have.
Oh, boy. Ha, ha.
(Penny:)What is it?
(Leonard:)It's a snowflake from the North Pole.
(Penny:)-Are you serious?
-Uh-huh.
(Leonard:)It'll last forever. I preserved it in a
1 -percent solution of polyvinyl acetal resin.
(Penny:)God, that's the most romantic thing
anyone's ever said to me...